Finding Aid for the Brainard Bartwell Cheney and Frances Neel Cheney Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Brainard Bartwell Cheney and Frances Neel Cheney Papers File Listing
  - Correspondence-Outgoing
    - September 25, 1959-October 8, 1959 (Box 4, File 24)
    - October 11, 1959-November 13, 1959 (Box 4, File 25)
    - November 15, 1959-December 19, 1959 (Box 4, File 26)
    - January 8, 1960-March 9, 1960 (Box 4, File 27)
    - March 12, 1960-May 17, 1960 (Box 4, File 28)
    - May 18, 1960-May 27, 1960 (Box 4, File 29)
    - June 1, 1960-June 30, 1960 (Box 4, File 30)
    - July 1, 1960-August 26, 1960 (Box 4, File 31)
    - September 5, 1960-September 28, 1960 (Box 4, File 32)
    - October 3, 1960-November 8, 1960 (Box 4, File 33)
    - November 10, 1960-December 23, 1960 (Box 4, File 34)
    - January 2, 1961-January 19, 1961 (Box 4, File 35)
    - January 22, 1961-March 23, 1961 (Box 4, File 36)
    - March 27, 1961-May 27, 1961 (Box 4, File 37)
    - June 3, 1961 (Box 4, File 38)
    - June 3, 1961-June 16, 1961 (Box 4, File 39)
    - July 18, 1961-December 16, 1961 (Box 4, File 40)
    - January 1, 1962-February 13, 1962 (Box 5, File 1)
    - February 19, 1962-April 25, 1962 (Box 5, File 2)
    - April 25, 1962-May 29, 1962 (Box 5, File 3)
    - August 6, 1962-October 23, 1962 (Box 5, File 4)
    - October 23, 1962-December 12, 1962 (Box 5, File 5)
    - January 3, 1963-March 3, 1963 (Box 5, File 6)
    - March 5, 1963-June 21, 1963 (Box 5, File 7)
    - July 1, 1963-September 30, 1963 (Box 5, File 8)
    - October 4, 1963-November 10, 1963 (Box 5, File 9)
    - November 12, 1963-December 15, 1963 (Box 5, File 10)
    - January 3, 1964-April 16, 1964 (Box 5, File 11)
    - April 20, 1964-July 14, 1964 (Box 5, File 12)
    - August 8, 1963-October 23, 1964 (Box 5, File 13)
    - October 27, 1964-December 18, 1964 (Box 5, File 14)
    - January 6, 1965-April 12, 1965 (Box 5, File 15)
    - April 20, 1965-June 27, 1965 (Box 5, File 16)
    - July 5, 1965-August 10, 1965 (Box 5, File 17)
    - September 11, 1965-October 31, 1965 (Box 5, File 18)
    - November 1, 1965-December 7, 1965 (Box 5, File 19)
    - January 5, 1966-February 20, 1966 (Box 5, File 20)
    - March 8, 1966-June 30, 1966 (Box 5, File 21)
    - July 1, 1966-October 22, 1966 (Box 5, File 22)
    - October 24, 1966-November 3, 1966 (Box 5, File 23)
    - November 8, 1966-December 27, 1966 (Box 5, File 24)
    - January 4, 1967-March 22, 1967 (Box 5, File 25)
    - April 2, 1967-May 30, 1967 (Box 5, File 26)
    - June 8, 1967-July 29, 1967 (Box 5, File 27)
    - August 3, 1967-October 6, 1967 (Box 5, File 28)
    - October 22, 1967-December 28, 1967 (Box 5, File 29)
    - January 1, 1968-January 31, 1968 (Box 5, File 30)
    - February 7, 1968-April 28, 1968 (Box 5, File 31)
    - May 1, 1968-June 20, 1968 (Box 5, File 32)
    - July 9, 1968-September 25, 1968 (Box 5, File 33)
    - September 28, 1968-December 14, 1968 (Box 5, File 34)
    - January 2, 1969-January 16, 1969 (Box 5, File 35)
    - January 17, 1969-March 20, 1969 (Box 5, File 36)
    - April 1, 1969-May 31, 1969 (Box 5, File 37)
    - June 8, 1969-September 25, 1969 (Box 5, File 38)
    - October 1, 1969-October 30, 1969 (Box 5, File 39)
    - November 9, 1969-December 10, 1969 (Box 5, File 40)
    - January 1, 1970-January 28, 1970 (Box 6, File 1)
    - February 3, 1970-April 15, 1970 (Box 6, File 2)
    - May 2, 1970-July 26, 1970 (Box 6, File 3)
    - August 13, 1970-September 26, 1970 (Box 6, File 4)
    - October 12, 1970-November 30, 1970 (Box 6, File 5)
    - December 2, 1970-December 23, 1970 (Box 6, File 6)
    - January 6, 1971-January 29, 1971 (Box 6, File 7)
    - February 2, 1971-March 29, 1971 (Box 6, File 8)
    - April 13, 1971-May 30, 1971 (Box 6, File 9)
    - June 11, 1971-July 22, 1971 (Box 6, File 10)
    - August 3, 1971-August 30, 1971 (Box 6, File 11)
    - September 1, 1971-September 28, 1971 (Box 6, File 12)
    - October 11, 1971-November 30, 1971 (Box 6, File 13)
    - December 3, 1971-December 31, 1971 (Box 6, File 14)
    - January 1, 1972-February 25, 1972 (Box 6, File 15)
    - March 4, 1972-April 11, 1972 (Box 6, File 16)
    - May 1, 1972-June 6, 1972 (Box 6, File 17)
    - June 21, 1972-July 28, 1972 (Box 6, File 18)
    - August 2, 1972-September 29, 1972 (Box 6, File 19)
    - October 3, 1972-November 7, 1972 (Box 6, File 20)
    - November 8, 1972-November 29, 1972 (Box 6, File 21)
    - December 7, 1972-December 25, 1972 (Box 6, File 22)
    - January 2, 1973-February 24, 1973 (Box 6, File 23)
    - March 1, 1973-March 26, 1973 (Box 6, File 24)
    - April 3, 1973-April 30, 1973 (Box 6, File 25)
    - May 7, 1973-June 19, 1973 (Box 6, File 26)
    - July 1, 1973-October 16, 1973 (Box 6, File 27)
    - November 7, 1973-December 31, 1973 (Box 6, File 28)
    - January 3, 1974-January 30, 1974 (Box 6, File 29)
    - February 8, 1974-February 23, 1974 (Box 6, File 30)
    - March 5, 1974-March 19, 1974 (Box 6, File 31)
    - April 1, 1974-April 23, 1974 (Box 6, File 32)
    - May 2, 1974-May 30, 1974 (Box 6, File 33)
    - June 1, 1974-July 30, 1974 (Box 6, File 34)
    - August 17, 1974-September 29, 1974 (Box 6, File 35)
    - October 4, 1974-October 30, 1974 (Box 6, File 36)
    - November 5, 1974-December 23, 1974 (Box 6, File 37)
    - January 4, 1975-January 6, 1975 (Box 7, File 1)
    - January 7, 1975-February 26, 1975 (Box 7, File 2)
    - March 4, 1975-April 30, 1975 (Box 7, File 3)
    - May 3, 1975-May 31, 1975 (Box 7, File 4)
    - June 2, 1975-June 28, 1975 (Box 7, File 5)
    - July 1, 1975-July 30, 1975 (Box 7, File 6)
    - August 6, 1975-September 35, 1975 (Box 7, File 7)
    - October 1, 1975-November 21, 1975 (Box 7, File 8)
    - December 3, 1975-December 27, 1975 (Box 7, File 9)
    - January 3, 1976-February 25, 1976 (Box 7, File 10)
    - March 6, 1976-April 30, 1976 (Box 7, File 11)
    - May 1, 1976-May 29, 1976 (Box 7, File 12)
    - June 5, 1976-June 28, 1976 (Box 7, File 13)
    - July 2, 1976-October 31, 1976 (Box 7, File 14)
    - November 17, 1976-December 27, 1976 (Box 7, File 15)
    - January 6, 1977-March 30, 1977 (Box 7, File 16)
    - April 11, 1977-August 19, 1977 (Box 7, File 17)
    - September 2, 1977-September 25, 1977 (Box 7, File 18)
    - October 13, 1977-November 29, 1977 (Box 7, File 19)
    - December 5, 1977-December 22, 1977 (Box 7, File 20)
    - January 2, 1978-February 25, 1977 (Box 7, File 21)
    - March 7, 1978-May 9, 1978 (Box 7, File 22)
    - June 1, 1978-June 11, 1978 (Box 7, File 23)
    - June 12, 1978-July 28, 1978 (Box 7, File 24)
    - August 14, 1978-October 29, 1978 (Box 7, File 25)
    - November 2, 1978-December 27, 1978 (Box 7, File 26)
    - January 5, 1979-January 28, 1979 (Box 7, File 27)
    - February 15, 1979-April 29, 1979 (Box 7, File 28)
    - May 5, 1979-June 29, 1979 (Box 7, File 29)
    - July 18, 1979-September 25, 1979 (Box 7, File 30)
    - October 16, 1979-December 11, 1979 (Box 7, File 31)
    - January 3, 1980-January 22, 1980 (Box 7, File 32)
    - February 6, 1980-April 25, 1980 (Box 7, File 33)
    - May 9, 1980-July 14, 1980 (Box 7, File 34)
    - August 5, 1980-August 31, 1980 (Box 7, File 35)
    - September 5, 1980-October 29, 1980 (Box 7, File 36)
    - November 14, 1980-November 30, 1980 (Box 7, File 37)
    - December 2, 1980-December 19, 1980 (Box 7, File 38)
    - January 2, 1981-February 11, 1981 (Box 8, File 1)
    - March 2, 1981-April 18, 1981 (Box 8, File 2)
    - April 19, 1981-June 24, 1981 (Box 8, File 3)
    - July 1, 1981-August 14, 1981 (Box 8, File 4)
    - August 20, 1981-September 17, 1981 (Box 8, File 5)
    - September 19, 1981-October 23, 1981 (Box 8, File 6)
    - November 1, 1981-December 29, 1981 (Box 8, File 7)
    - January 1, 1982-January 29, 1982 (Box 8, File 8)
    - February 3, 1982-February 25, 1982 (Box 8, File 9)
    - March 4, 1982-March 28, 1982 (Box 8, File 10)
    - April 15, 1982-May 15, 1982 (Box 8, File 11)
    - May 21, 1982-June 29, 1982 (Box 8, File 12)
    - July 5, 1982-August 31, 1982 (Box 8, File 13)
    - September 3, 1982-December 20, 1982 (Box 8, File 14)
    - January 5, 1983-February 28, 1983 (Box 8, File 15)
    - March 7, 1983-April 29, 1983 (Box 8, File 16)
    - May 9, 1983-August 31, 1983 (Box 8, File 17)
    - September 2, 1983-December 14, 1983 (Box 8, File 18)
    - January 23, 1984-April 27, 1984 (Box 8, File 19)
    - May 7, 1984-July 25, 1984 (Box 8, File 20)
    - August 1, 1984-December 17, 1984 (Box 8, File 21)
    - January 14, 1985-March 20, 1985 (Box 8, File 22)
    - April 2, 1985-December 31, 1985 (Box 8, File 23)
    - April 15, 1986-May 5, 1986 (Box 8, File 24)
    - Undated (Box 8, File 25)
    - Undated (Box 8, File 26)
    - Undated (Box 8, File 27)
    - Undated (Box 8, File 28)
    - Undated (Box 8, File 29)
    - Undated (Box 8, File 30)
    - Undated (Box 8, File 31)
  - Correspondence-Incoming
    - Abelson, Philip-Anderson, Mary (Box 9, File 1)
    - Anderson,William-Ayers, Gaylord (Box 9, File 2)
    - Bain, David-Bandy, Alice (Box 9, File 3)
    - Bandy, Carol- Bandy, William (Box 9, File 4)
    - Banks, Harvey- Bartley, Robert (Box 9, File 5)
    - Bass, Frank- Beatty, Richmond, (October 14, 1940-December 29, 1944) (Box 9, File 6)
    - Beatty, Richmond, (October 29, 1960- Undated)- Beede, Ivan (Box 9, File 7)
    - Bell, Allen- Berg, Norman (Box 9, File 8)
    - Bess, George- Bess, Robin, (July 21, 1934-December 21, 1940) (Box 9, File 9)
    - Bess, Robin, (December 24, 1942-February 12, 1952) (Box 9, File 10)
    - Bess, Sarah- Bleasby, George (Box 9, File 11)
    - Blease, Eugene- Bozone, Billie (Box 9, File 12)
    - Brandon, Albert- Brandon, Martha, (March 26, 1939-June 9, 1942) (Box 9, File 13)
    - Brandon, Martha, (July 15, 1942-November 15, 1947) (Box 9, File 14)
    - Brandon, Martha, (January 10, 1948-December 15, 1951) (Box 9, File 15)
    - Brandon, Martha, (February 16, 1952-October 17, 1955) (Box 9, File 16)
    - Brandon, Martha, (January 6, 1956-August 17, 1964) (Box 9, File 17)
    - Brandon, Martha, (August 17, 1965-July 1, 1971) (Box 9, File 18)
    - Brandon, Martha, (January 6, 1972-July 17, 1974) (Box 9, File 19)
    - Brandon, Martha, ( March 17, 1975- Undated) (Box 9, File 20)
    - Brandon, Newman- Brooks, Cleanth (Box 9, File 21)
    - Brooks, Tinkham- Brooks, Paul (Box 9, File 22)
    - Brooks, Paul, (January 14, 1941-June 28, 1955) (Box 9, File 23)
    - Brown, Ashley, (June 24, 1958-December 13, 1975) (Box 10, File 1)
    - Brown, Ashley, (January 10, 1976-November 27, 1978) (Box 10, File 2)
    - Brown, Ashley, (January 4, 1979-December 24, 1980) (Box 10, File 3)
    - Brown, Ashley, (March 1, 1981-December 22, 1983) (Box 10, File 4)
    - Brown, Ashley, (May 27, 1984- Undated)- Brown, Jerry (Box 10, File 5)
    - Brown, Susan Jenkins, (October 5, 1954-December 18, 1960) (Box 10, File 6)
    - Brown, Susan Jenkins, (August 21, 1961- Undated) (Box 10, File 7)
    - Bruce, J.F. - Bryan, Jr., Charles F. (Box 10, File 8)
    - Bryan, Edith, (January 8, 1956-June 21, 1982) (Box 10, File 9)
    - Buckley, Pricilla- Butler, Hilton (Box 10, File 10)
    - Caldwell, John, (March 10, 1955-May 9, 1958) (Box 10, File 11)
    - Caldwell, John, (July 29, 1958-June 16, 1960) (Box 10, File 12)
    - Caldwell, John, (July 7, 1960- Undated)- Carter, Don (Box 10, File 13)
    - Carter, Hodding- Carter, Thomas (Box 10, File 14)
    - Carver, Catherine- Cheney, David (Box 10, File 15)
    - Cheney, Ray- Childe, C.E. (Box 10, File 16)
    - Clap, Bob- Clement, Frank (Box 10, File 17)
    - Cline, Helen- Cole, Elizabeth (Box 10, File 18)
    - Collier, David- Connell, Leigh (Box 10, File 19)
    - Cooney, Marjorie- Cossey, Cecil (Box 10, File 20)
    - Costa, Alan- Cowely, Muriel (Box 10, File 21)
    - Cowley, Robert- Cushman, Joseph (Box 10, File 22)
    - Daniel, Robert- Davidson, Donald (Box 11, File 1)
    - Davidson, W.W. - Decker, C.F. (Box 11, File 2)
    - Delbruck, Manny- Dimler, G. Richard (Box 11, File 3)
    - Dorsey, Jack- Drown, Jeanne (Box 11, File 4)
    - East, Charles- Evins, Joe L. (Box 11, File 5)
    - Faber, Robert- Fajardo, E. Rogue (Box 11, File 6)
    - Fajardo, Rose Ellen- Fisher, Dorothy (Box 11, File 7)
    - FitzGerald, Benedict- FitzGerald, Stephanie (Box 11, File 8)
    - FitzGerald, William- Foley, Andrew (Box 11, File 9)
    - Ford, Ruth- Fraistat, Rose Ann (Box 11, File 10)
    - Francis, Warren- Fuller, Edmund (Box 11, File 11)
    - Gallup, George- Giniger, K.S. (Box 11, File 12)
    - Giroux, Robert- Goodman, B.B. (Box 11, File 13)
    - Gordon, Caroline, (March 1932-December 20, 1939) (Box 11, File 14)
    - Gordon, Caroline, (October 24, 1941-May 24, 1945) (Box 11, File 15)
    - Gordon, Caroline, (April 12, 1947-November 13, 1950) (Box 11, File 16)
    - Gordon, Caroline, (February 23, 1951-December 31, 1951) (Box 11, File 17)
    - Gordon, Caroline, (February 16, 1952-July 6, 1953) (Box 11, File 18)
    - Gordon, Caroline, (February 19, 1954-August 9, 1954) (Box 11, File 19)
    - Gordon, Caroline, (April 18, 1955-November 15, 1957) (Box 11, File 20)
    - Gordon, Caroline, (Spring 1958-February 15, 1979) (Box 11, File 21)
    - Gordon, Caroline (Undated) (Box 11, File 22)
    - Gordon, Caroline (Undated) (Box 11, File 23)
    - Gordon, Caroline (Undated) (Box 11, File 24)
    - Gordon, Caroline (Undated) (Box 11, File 25)
    - Gordon, Caroline (Undated) (Box 11, File 26)
    - Gore, Albert- Goren, Ruth (Box 12, File 1)
    - Gotto, Antonio, (July 11, 1967-January 20, 1982) (Box 12, File 2)
    - Govan, Gilbert- Greene, Lee (Box 12, File 3)
    - Grennen, Joseph- Grisham, Frank (Box 12, File 4)
    - Haddock, Susan- Hale, Winfield (Box 12, File 5)
    - Hall, Martha- Hatumaka, Kyoko (Box 12, File 6)
    - Haun, Mildred, (December 2, 1943- Undated) (Box 12, File 7)
    - Havens, Annette- Heard, Jean (Box 12, File 8)
    - Hearne, Mary Glenn- Hitchcock, James (Box 12, File 9)
    - Hollis, C. Carroll- Houghton Mifflin Company (Box 12, File 10)
    - Howard, Iris Graves- Hutton, Marilyn (Box 12, File 11)
    - Isaacson, George- Iwasaki, Shuku (Box 12, File 12)
    - Jackson, Janet- Jessep, William Eugene (Box 12, File 13)
    - Jewell, Tisa- Jordan, R. F. (Box 12, File 14)
    - Joseph, Nannine, (March 10, 1937-September 2, 1941) (Box 12, File 15)
    - Joseph, Nannine, (January 15, 1942-December 28, 1942) (Box 12, File 16)
    - Joseph, Nannine, (March 4, 1943-September 14, 1951)- Josey, Buck (Box 12, File 17)
    - Kaser, David- Kennedy, Robert (Box 12, File 18)
    - Kenney, W. Henry- Kirk, John (Box 12, File 19)
    - Kirk, Russell, (March 20, 1954-July 11, 1958) (Box 12, File 20)
    - Kirk, Russell, (January 23, 1959-July 1, 1969) (Box 12, File 21)
    - Kirk, Russell, (February 11, 1972-December 16, 1988) (Box 12, File 22)
    - Kittredge, Winifred- Krug, Thomas (Box 12, File 23)
    - Larkins, Rose Ann- Lanier, Lyle (Box 12, File 24)
    - Latham, H.S. - LeQuire, Virgil (Box 12, File 25)
    - Lewis, H.D. - Lucas, Mary King (Box 12, File 26)
    - Lukacs, John, (June 28, 1970- Undated) (Box 12, File 27)
    - Lurie, Mara- Lyle, Virginia (Box 12, File 28)
    - Lytle, Andrew, (November 24, 1938-July 21, 1947) (Box 13, File 1)
    - Lytle, Andrew, (March 19, 1948-December 1, 1953) (Box 13, File 2)
    - Lytle, Andrew, (February 2, 1954-September 23, 1964) (Box 13, File 3)
    - Lytle, Andrew, (February 5, 1968-June 20, 1983) (Box 13, File 4)
    - Lytle, Andrew (Undated)- Lytle, Langdon (Box 13, File 5)
    - Macauley, Robie- Martin, Frank (Box 13, File 6)
    - Martin, Harold- McCall, Monica (Box 13, File 7)
    - McCaslin, Ann- McDowell, David, (October 14, 1957-September 19, 1958) (Box 13, File 8)
    - McDowell, David, (January 13, 1959-October 26, 1966) (Box 13, File 9)
    - McDowell, David, (August 15, 1967-November 16, 1973) (Box 13, File 10)
    - McDowell, David, (September 10, 1974- Undated) (Box 13, File 11)
    - McGlacher, Edward- McGill, Ralph (Box 13, File 12)
    - McGuire, Harry- McNeil, Blanche (Box 13, File 13)
    - McRae, Duncan- McVoy, E.J. (Box 13, File 14)
    - Mendelsohn, Max- Michael, Paul (Box 13, File 15)
    - Mihanovich, Clement- Mims, Catherine, (November 28, 1963-August 18, 1974) (Box 13, File 16)
    - Mims, Catherine, (March 6, 1975-December 28, 1975) (Box 13, File 17)
    - Mims, Catherine, (January 11, 1976-December 26, 1977) (Box 13, File 18)
    - Mims, Catherine, (March 20, 1978-October 16, 1981) (Box 13, File 19)
    - Mims, Catherine, (May 25, 1982-June 12, 1988) (Box 13, File 20)
    - Mims, Catherine (Undated)- Mims, Ella Puryear (Box 13, File 21)
    - Minow, Newton- Mobley, John, (November 22, 1939-October 16, 1971) (Box 14, File 1)
    - Mobley, John, (January 24, 1972-December 13, 1984) (Box 14, File 2)
    - Mobley, John (Undated)- Montgomery, Marion (Box 14, File 3)
    - Mood, M.L.- Mood, Toby, (April 20, 1971-September 23, 1972) (Box 14, File 4)
    - Mood, Toby, (January 20, 1973-November 18, 1980) (Box 14, File 5)
    - Mood, Toby, (January 27, 1981- Undated) (Box 14, File 6)
    - Morrison, Carlton- Myrer, Patricia (Box 14, File 7)
    - Nagasawa, Masao- Neel, Collier (Box 14, File 8)
    - Neel, Roy, (April 30, 1980-October 22, 1982) (Box 14, File 9)
    - Neel, Roy, (June 24, 1983- Undated) (Box 14, File 10)
    - Neel, T. Meeks- O’Conner, Regina (Box 14, File 11)
    - O’Connor, Flannery, (February 8, 1953-December 2, 1955) (Box 14, File 12)
    - O’Connor, Flannery, (February 18, 1956-October 18, 1956) (Box 14, File 13)
    - O’Connor, Flannery, (January 3, 1957-December 2, 1958) (Box 14, File 14)
    - O’Connor, Flannery, (February 22, 1959-December 10, 1959) (Box 14, File 15)
    - O’Connor, Flannery, (February 6, 1960-November 24, 1962) (Box 14, File 16)
    - O’Connor, Flannery, (January 13, 1963- Undated) (Box 14, File 17)
    - Ogden, Archibald- Owsley, Harriet (Box 14, File 18)
    - Padgett, Caroline- Pearson, Eugene (Box 14, File 19)
    - Pearson, Margaret- Pendleton, W. Barry (Box 14, File 20)
    - Percy, Walker- Sister Peterkin (Box 14, File 21)
    - Petrie, Garner- Pick, John (Box 14, File 22)
    - Pickrel, Paul- Prescott, Joseph (Box 14, File 23)
    - Presley, Delma, (July 20, 1973-November 25, 1981) (Box 14, File 24)
    - Presley, Delma, (January 8, 1982- Spring 1986)- Puryear, Sarah (Box 14, File 25)
    - Quenzel, Carrol- Quinn, John (Box 15, File 1)
    - WR- Rey, Veronica (Box 15, File 2)
    - Reynolds, Horace-Rostow, W.W. (Box 15, File 3)
    - Rothstein, Samuel- Russo, Francis (Box 15, File 4)
    - Russo, Mary Allen, (February 28, 1949-December 28, 1949) (Box 15, File 5)
    - Russo, Mary Allen, (March 27, 1950- Undated) (Box 15, File 6)
    - Ryals, Jimmy- Ryan, Pat (Box 15, File 7)
    - Samples, M. David- Scott, Zachary (Box 15, File 8)
    - Sebring, Harold- Silvia, Catherine (Box 15, File 9)
    - Simpson, Lewis- Smith, Lou Ann (Box 15, File 10)
    - Smith, Willa, (September 27, 1958-October 7, 1972) (Box 15, File 11)
    - Smith, Willa, (March 3, 1975-June 25, 1975) (Box 15, File 12)
    - Smith, Willa, (August 9, 1975-June 3, 1982) (Box 15, File 13)
    - Smith, Willa, (September 27, 1982-Undated)-Southern Review (Box 15, File 14)
    - Spears, Monroe- Stamps, Martha Cheney (Box 15, File 15)
    - Starr, Alfred- Stephens, Leila (Box 15, File 16)
    - Stewart, Randall- Stratford, Charles (Box 15, File 17)
    - Strauss, Helen, (July 13, 1949-September 19, 1956) (Box 15, File 18)
    - Stritch, Thomas, (February 12, 1952-April 11, 1966) (Box 15, File 19)
    - Stritch, Thomas, (August 31, 1968-July 29, 1975) (Box 15, File 20)
    - Stritch, Thomas, (January 13, 1976-January 1, 1989) (Box 15, File 21)
    - Stritch, Thomas (Undated) (Box 15, File 22)
    - Stubbs, Sidney- Stubbs, Thomas, (November 18, 1972-December 28, 1972) (Box 15, File 23)
    - Stubbs, Thomas, (January 20, 1973-Undated) (Box 15, File 24)
    - Sturdevant, William- Swidler, Joseph (Box 15, File 25)
    - Takashi, Kiyonaga- Tate, Allen, (December 7, 1938-June 21, 1943) (Box 16, File 1)
    - Tate, Allen, (July 18, 1944-November 8, 1955) (Box 16, File 2)
    - Tate, Allen, (February 12, 1957-November 17, 1966) (Box 16, File 3)
    - Tate, Allen, (January 11, 1967- Undated) (Box 16, File 4)
    - Tate, Ben- Tate, Helen, (September 30, 1967-December 25, 1968) (Box 16, File 5)
    - Tate, Helen, (January 10, 1969-December 24, 1975) (Box 16, File 6)
    - Tate, Helen, (January 3, 1976-December 17, 1979) (Box 16, File 7)
    - Tate, Helen, (December 10, 1980-December 16, 1988) (Box 16, File 8)
    - Tate, Helen (Undated)- Taylor, Eleanor (Box 16, File 9)
    - Taylor, Peter- Taylor, Tucky, (September 20, 1962-August 9, 1967) (Box 16, File 10)
    - Taylor, Tucky, (February 1, 1968-February 9, 1969) (Box 16, File 11)
    - Taylor, Tucky, (March 17, 1972-December 9, 1979) (Box 16, File 12)
    - Taylor, Tucky, (November 2, 1980- Undated)-TeSelle, Sallie (Box 16, File 13)
    - Thompson, Alice-Vidrine, Catherine Townsend (Box 16, File 14)
    - Wade, Irving- Waldrop, Frank (Box 16, File 15)
    - Walker, Eugene- Wallsup, Katherine (Box 16, File 16)
    - Walsh, Jack, (April 24, 1959-December 8, 1960) (Box 16, File 17)
    - Walsh, Jack, (January 17, 1961-April 7, 1966)- Warder, Margaret (Box 16, File 18)
    - Warren, Cinina- Warren, Eleanor (Box 16, File 19)
    - Warren, Robert Penn, (November 13, 1939-July 5, 1949) (Box 16, File 20)
    - Warren, Robert Penn, (October 25, 1950-October 28, 1955) (Box 16, File 21)
    - Warren, Robert Penn, (March 5, 1956-March 31, 1960) (Box 16, File 22)
    - Warren, Robert Penn, (May 19, 1961-May 26, 1969) (Box 16, File 23)
    - Warren, Robert Penn, (February 19, 1970- Undated)- Warren, Rosanna (Box 16, File 24)
    - Washburn, Susanne- Wells, Joel (Box 16, File 25)
    - Weeks, Caroline- White, Bradford (Box 17, File 1)
    - Whitfield, Joanne- Wills II, William Ridley (Box 17, File 2)
    - Wilson, James- Wood, Helen (Box 17, File 3)
    - Wood, Nancy Tate- Wright, Louis (Box 17, File 4)
    - Wright, Stuart- Wroton, Charles Lang (Box 17, File 5)
    - Yaddo- Young, Jim (Box 17, File 6)
    - Zibart, Alan- Zimmer, Paul (Box 17, File 7)
    - Unidentified (Box 17, File 8)
    - Unidentified (Box 17, File 9)
    - Unidentified (Box 17, File 10)
    - Unidentified (Box 17, File 11)
  - Writings, Manuscripts
  - Lightwood
    - Version A, Chapters 1-4 (Box 18, File 1)
    - Version A, Chapters 5-8 (Box 18, File 2)
    - Version A, Chapters 9-12 (Box 18, File 3)
    - Version A, Chapters 13-16 (Box 18, File 4)
    - Version A, Chapters 17-20 (Box 18, File 5)
    - Version A, Chapters 21-24 (Box 18, File 6)
    - Version A, Chapters 25-29 (no Chapter 27) (Box 18, File 7)
    - Version A, Chapters 30-34 (Box 18, File 8)
    - Version A, Chapters 35-36 (plus various corrections) (Box 18, File 9)
    - Version B, Chapters 1-5 (Box 18, File 10)
    - Version B, Chapters 6-10 (Box 18, File 11)
    - Version B, Chapters 11-15 (Box 18, File 12)
    - Version B, Chapters 16-20 (Box 18, File 13)
    - Version B, Chapters 21-26 (Box 18, File 14)
    - Version B, Chapters 27-31 (Box 18, File 15)
    - Version B, Chapters 32-37 (Box 18, File 16)
    - Serialized in Scribner’s Commentator, November 1939-January 1940 (Box 18, File 17)
    - Forward for Second Printing (Box 19, File 1)
    - Fragments, Chapters 1-8 (Box 19, File 2)
    - Fragments (Box 19, File 3)
    - Fragments (Box 19, File 4)
  - River Rogue
    - Chapter 1 (Box 19, File 5)
    - Chapter 2 (Box 19, File 6)
    - Chapter 3 (Box 19, File 7)
    - Chapter 4 (Box 19, File 8)
    - Chapter 5 (Box 19, File 9)
    - Chapter 6 (Box 19, File 10)
    - Chapter 7 (Box 19, File 11)
    - Chapter 8 (Box 19, File 12)
    - Chapter 9 (Box 19, File 13)
    - Chapters 10-11 (Box 19, File 14)
    - Chapters 12-13 (Box 19, File 15)
    - Chapter 14 (Box 19, File 16)
    - Chapter 15 (Box 19, File 17)
    - Chapter 16 (Box 19, File 18)
    - Chapter 17 (Box 19, File 19)